A Guide to the Papers of Archie G. Richardson 1918-1976
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
Special Collections and Archives, Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
A Guide to the Papers of Archie G. Richardson 1918-1976
Special Collections and Archives, Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
1997-77
20,000 Pieces
In 1936, Archie Richardson became the highest-ranking African American in the State Government. In that year, he was appointed assistant to the Assistant for Negro education in Virginia. In 1969, he retired as Associate Director of the Division of Secondary Education in Virginia. His papers consist of correspondence, speeches, writings and more than one thousand photographs of Rosenwald, Slater, and other schools constructed in Virginia for African Americans in the 1930's and before. Acc. #1997-77 Arranged By: Lucious Edwards
The Richardson Papers were given as a gift of the Richardson Family.
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Biographical/Historical Information
Archie Gibbs Richardson, was the Associate Director of the Division of Secondary Education, State Department of Education, Richmond, Virginia. He was born in Lexington, Virginia, April 4, 1904. Because there were few high schools for African American in Virginia, Richardson's parents sent him to the high school at the Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute at Petersburg where he completed the program in 1923. He received the B.A. Degree from Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute, Petersburg, in June 1927; the M.S. Degree in education from Butler University, Indianapolis, Indiana, in June 1939; and was granted the degree of Doctor of Education at Columbia University, New York, in1946. In June 1957, Virginia State College conferred upon him the honorary degree of Doctor of Laws.
Richardson served as principal of the Mecklenburg County Training School, in South Hill, Virginia, 1927-1935; and as Director of academics at Saint Paul Normal School, Lawrenceville, Virginia. The State Superintendent of Public Instruction appointed him Assistant Supervisor of "Negro" Education in 1936. On January 1, 1951, he was promoted to the position of Associate Supervisor of Elementary and Secondary Education. He received another promotion on September 1, 1966, to Associate Director of the Division of Secondary Education. He retired April 4, 1969.
Richardson had two elementary schools and one high school named for him. The elementary schools were in Culpepper and the other in Blackstone, Virginia. Archie Richardson High School was located in Louisa County, Virginia.
During his tenure, he contributed a number of articles to State and National journals of education. He also authored The Development of Negro Education in Virginia.
Mr. Richardson was married to Linnie Ramey for over fifty years. Mrs. Richardson taught at schools in Mecklenburg and Richmond, Virginia.
Scope and Content Information
How did Virginia explain educational public policy during the era of legal segregation? Archie Richardson's main responsibility during his tenure with the Department of Education was that of official spokesman to the African American Community for the State of Virginia. Correspondence, speeches, writings, and photographs documenting Archie Richardson's position as the only African American professional employed by the Education Department in Virginia during the era of legal segregation, Constitutes the majority of these materials.
Series Description
Series I. Correspondence 1932-1979 Personal and Business Boxes 1-3
Sub-series A: Correspondence by subject Correspondence, most generated by Richardson during his tenure with the department of Education. Arranged Alphabetically and then chronologically within the folders.
Sub-series B: Correspondence by date Arranged Chronologically.
Series II. Literary Boxes 4-19
Sub-Series A: Speeches Arranged by title and date, followed by speeches with dates and materials missing both a date and a clearly defined title.
Sub-Series B: Writings and Reports Some of the writings were used later in Richardson's history of Negro education in Virginia. Many of the reports appear to have been used by Richardson to carry out his job with the State Department of Education. The reports consist of conference and workshop results organized by Richardson.
Sub-Series C: Research Notes During Richardson's career, part of his responsibility was to develop procedures and manuals used by African-American Schools in Virginia. This sub-series also contains an interesting log concerning the Whitcomb court school in Richmond, VA.
Series III. Video Recordings Taped speeches at different functions attended by Richardson. Most of the speeches were not delivered by Richardson.
Series IV: Photographs Boxes 21-27
Sub-series A: Family and Personal Photo's of activities at Virginia State when Richardson was a student and later as a teacher at the Mecklenburg County Training School, conferences at Virginia State and other areas.
Sub-series B: Education in Virginia (African American Schools) Several thousand 3x5 black and white photographs and negatives of schools scenes in Virginia. The Photographs were taken between the years 1926 and 1938. The Photographs and negatives are of European, Native, and African American school buildings, some classes, and other activities. Most of the developed photographs are of African American schools and include Rosenwald, Slater, and other buildings used by African Americans in Virginia. *The origin of the photographs and negatives is not known. The folders are arranged alphabetically by county and city.
Sub-series C. Negatives of the schools and scenes located in some of Virginia's counties and cities. These do not have an inventory, but are arranged by county and city. In addition there are negatives of activities relating to education outside of the state of Virginia.
Box #28 Series V: Scrapbooks and Yearbooks Correspondence most of which covers Richardson's retirement, two yearbooks from Louisa, Virginia.
Series VI: Printed Printed items including certificates, pamphlets, and degrees
Box #29 Sub-series A: Awards and Certificates Awards and certificates presented to Richardson over the years.
Sub-series B: Pamphlets Two items: one the By-Laws of the Southside Interscholastic Athletic Association, documenting an early effort to organize African American sports played in the high schools.
Sub-series C: Book The Development of Negro Education in Virginia, 1831-1970, published by Phi Delta Kappa.
Sub-series D: Degrees Earned Degrees of Archie and Linnie Richardson
Box #30 Series-series E: News clippings News clippings from a number of newspapers primary from the state of Virginia.
Contents List
- Correspondence-Personal and Business 1932-1979
  - By Subject
    - Alpha Phi Alpha 1970-1973 (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha 1974-1977 (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Art 1966-1971 (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Bedford County 1947-1950 (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Bedford County 1951-1952 (Box-folder 1:5)
    - Black Education in Virginia 1975 (Box-folder 1:6)
    - Citizenship (Box-folder 1:7)
    - Committees Teacher Education 1969-1975 (Box-folder 1:8)
    - Curriculum-Education, Supervisors, Schools 1942,1959 (Box-folder 1:9)
    - Curriculum (Box-folder 1:10)
    - Eastview Civic League 1961,1976 (Box-folder 1:11)
    - Education of the Negro-Project 1968-1976 (Box-folder 1:12)
    - Evaluation 1960 (Box-folder 1:13)
    - The Gaines Case 1938 (Box-folder 1:14)
    - GED 1969 (Box-folder 1:15)
    - General Education Developement Program 1969,1971 (Box-folder 1:16)
    - Hampton Institute 1959,62-64 (Box-folder 1:17)
    - Hampton Institute 1964-1968 (Box-folder 1:18)
    - Negro History 1965-1968 (Box-folder 2:1)
    - Newport News Salary Care 1945 (Box-folder 2:2)
    - Mrs. Overby 1975 (Box-folder 2:3)
    - Mrs.Overby (Box-folder 2:4)
    - Personal Data 1945-1949,1964 (Box-folder 2:5)
    - Phi Delta Kappa 1970 (Box-folder 2:6)
    - Pulaski County 1949 (Box-folder 2:7)
    - Pulaski County 1949-1950 (Box-folder 2:8)
    - Retirement 1942,1969 (Box-folder 2:9)
    - School Desegregation in Virginia (Box-folder 2:10)
    - State Board of Education 1952,1963 (Box-folder 2:11)
    - State Board of Education (Box-folder 2:12)
    - Status Reports on Virginia Education 1964-1966 (Box-folder 2:13)
    - State Reports on Education in Virginia 1967 (Box-folder 2:14)
    - Surry County 1948 (Box-folder 2:15)
    - Teachers (new course) approval 1965 (Box-folder 2:16)
    - Vocational Education 1968,1970 (Box-folder 2:17)
    - VRTA Bicentennial Committee (Box-folder 2:18)
  - Correspondence
    - Correspondence 1932,1937 (Box-folder 3:1)
    - Correspondence 1943-1955 (Box-folder 3:2)
    - Correspondence 1956-1963 (Box-folder 3:3)
    - Correspondence 1964-1967 (Box-folder 3:4)
    - Correspondence 1968-1969 (Box-folder 3:5)
    - Correspondence 1970 (Box-folder 3:6)
    - Correspondence 1971-1972 (Box-folder 3:7)
    - Correspondence 1973-1974 (Box-folder 3:8)
    - Correspondence 1975-1977 (Box-folder 3:9)
    - Correspondence 1978-1979 (Box-folder 3:10)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 3:11)
- Literary
  - Speeches (By Date)
    - Music in the Total School Program 1934 (Box-folder 4:1)
    - Statement to the Associated Negro Press 1937 (Box-folder 4:2)
    - Improvements made in Negro Education 1939 (Box-folder 4:3)
    - The College and it's relationship to Virginia Culture 1939 (Box-folder 4:4)
    - Hampton Institute Past Present and Future 1939 (Box-folder 4:5)
    - Some Factors Affecting the Education of Negroes for Citizenship 1939 (Box-folder 4:6)
    - Our Schools Challenged by Our Culture in Transition Sept. 24, 1943 (Box-folder 4:7)
    - Trends in Evaluating Pupik Achievement 1945 (Box-folder 4:8)
    - Public Education in Virginia 1949 (Box-folder 4:9)
    - Supervising Instruction in High School 1949 (Box-folder 4:10)
    - Public Education Instruction in Virginia 1949 (Box-folder 4:11)
    - Some Suggestions for Eliminating Difficulties in Reading Through Studying and Understanding Students 1949 (Box-folder 4:12)
    - Teaching as a Career 1950 (Box-folder 4:13)
    - John Dewey 1952 (Box-folder 4:14)
    - Simulation and Gaming 1956 (Box-folder 4:15)
    - Maintaining Balance in the Education Program 1956 (Box-folder 4:16)
    - What Researchers Say About Grouping Children 1958 (Box-folder 4:17)
    - A Non-Graded Program 1959 (Box-folder 4:18)
    - Fellowship in Action 1960 (Box-folder 4:19)
    - Hindsight-Foresight and Insight 1961 (Box-folder 4:20)
    - Some Factors Affecting Teaching 1961 (Box-folder 4:21)
    - Why in Service Education? 1962 (Box-folder 4:22)
    - How Parents Can help to Raise the Acheivement Level of Children 1962 (Box-folder 4:23)
    - An Echo 1963 (Box-folder 4:24)
    - Home of the Brave 1963 (Box-folder 4:25)
    - Teaching is not an Instruction 1963 (Box-folder 4:26)
    - Dr. Richardson Speaks to the Third District Principals and Supervisors 1964 (Box-folder 4:27)
    - How to Motivate Learning 1964 (Box-folder 4:28)
    - The Relationship of Health to Academic Acheivement 1965 (Box-folder 4:29)
    - A Reading Program Based on Needs 1965 (Box-folder 4:30)
    - Increased Educational Responsibilities of the Principal in Today's School 1966 (Box-folder 4:31)
    - A look at Where We Now Stand As Negro Principals 1966 (Box-folder 4:32)
    - You Finish to Begin 1966 (Box-folder 4:33)
    - A Look At Where We Now Stand As Negro Principals 1967 (Box-folder 4:34)
    - A Message of Dedication 1967 (Box-folder 4:35)
    - A Look At Where We Now Stand As Negro Principals 1967 (Box-folder 4:36)
    - The Relationship of Health and Academic Achievement 1967 (Box-folder 4:37)
    - Implementing of Language Arts in Other Subject Area's 1967 (Box-folder 4:38)
    - Large was Our Bounty 1967 (Box-folder 4:39)
    - A Presentation to One Who Deserves it 1968 (Box-folder 4:40)
    - Words About The Author 1968 (Box-folder 4:41)
    - Be Not Dismayed-Take Care of Yourself 1968 (Box-folder 4:42)
    - School Administration 1968 (Box-folder 4:43)
    - Yesterday,Today, and Tomorrow 1968 (Box-folder 4:44)
    - Decision Making In Instruction 1968 (Box-folder 4:45)
    - Accepting the Challenge 1970 (Box-folder 4:46)
    - The War of Arms is Ended but the War of Ideas Lingers on 1973 (Box-folder 4:47)
    - A Presentation to One Who Deserves it 1973 (Box-folder 4:48)
  - Speeches (title and no date)
    - A Good School Principal (Box-folder 5:1)
    - Arguments Against Carrying Out a Decision (Box-folder 5:2)
    - A Message of Dedication (Box-folder 5:3)
    - The Revolution in Education (Box-folder 5:4)
    - Team Teaching (Box-folder 5:5)
    - The Importance of Efficient Leadership in the Church Today (Box-folder 5:6)
    - Modern Trends in Education (Box-folder 5:7)
    - The Non-Graded Program (Box-folder 5:8)
    - Teachers: Questions Determine the Quality of Thinking Pupils Develop (Box-folder 5:9)
    - Legal Responsibilities of Primiyids (Box-folder 5:10)
    - Problems to be Faced (Box-folder 5:11)
    - Youth Today,Leaders Tommorow (Box-folder 5:12)
    - Welcome to the Mathematics Conference (Box-folder 5:13)
    - Panel Discussion: How to Help Various Types of Disaffected Children (Box-folder 5:14)
    - The Present Status of Negro Education in Virginia (Box-folder 5:15)
    - Effectiveness in working with others (Box-folder 5:16)
    - Infinite Progression (Box-folder 5:17)
    - Increased Educational Responsibilities of the Principals in today's schools (Box-folder 5:18)
    - Providing a Balanced School Program (Box-folder 5:19)
    - Improving Instruction in Schools and Colleges (Box-folder 5:20)
    - Education Moves Freedom Forward (Box-folder 5:21)
    - Large was our Bounty (Box-folder 5:22)
    - Toward Excellence (Box-folder 5:23)
    - An Instructional Program in Evaluation (Box-folder 5:24)
    - A Parable (Box-folder 5:25)
    - The Courier Journal, The Louisville Times (Box-folder 5:26)
    - Recognition of Creative Ability (Box-folder 5:27)
    - Leading Youth in a World in Conflict (Box-folder 5:28)
    - Commitment to Improved Instruction (Box-folder 5:29)
    - How to Motivate Children to Learn (Box-folder 5:30)
    - How to help Various Types of Disaffected Children (Box-folder 5:31)
    - Choosing a Career (Box-folder 5:32)
    - What is Teaching (Box-folder 5:33)
    - The Characteristics of a Good School Principal (Box-folder 5:34)
    - Human Unrest and the challenge for living better (Box-folder 5:35)
    - Promotion and Failure (Box-folder 5:36)
    - I Acted as Their Advocate (Box-folder 5:37)
    - The Joy of Life is Living it (Box-folder 5:38)
    - More Quality Need in Education (Box-folder 5:39)
    - Programmed Learning (Box-folder 5:40)
    - Samples of Learning (Box-folder 5:41)
    - Working for Great Ideas (Box-folder 5:42)
    - The Effects of Cultural Deprivation Upon the School Achievement of Negro Children (Box-folder 5:43)
    - Speech-Summary (Box-folder 5:44)
    - Freedom and Public Education (Box-folder 5:45)
    - Aims,Objectives and Organizations of the Student Council (Box-folder 5:46)
    - Foreign Language Conference (Box-folder 5:47)
    - Techniques Used in Working in the Field (Box-folder 5:48)
    - Quality Teaching and Quality Instruction (Box-folder 6:1)
    - Understanding (Box-folder 6:2)
    - Service in Elementary School (Box-folder 6:3)
    - Summary of Drive in Conference at Manassas (Box-folder 6:4)
    - Enrichment in the Instruction of Gifted Children and Youth (Box-folder 6:5)
    - Techniques used in Working the Field (Box-folder 6:6)
    - Balancing the Curriculum Through Fine Arts (Box-folder 6:7)
    - Show Me How (Box-folder 6:8)
    - Negro Principals (Box-folder 6:9)
    - Teaching Today (Box-folder 6:10)
    - How to Bring About Better Articulation Between the Elementary and High School (Box-folder 6:11)
    - Bulletin to Teachers (Box-folder 6:12)
    - A Proposed Conference on the Supervision of Student Teachers (Box-folder 6:13)
    - Guidance (Box-folder 6:14)
    - Fundamentals and Techniques of Human Relations (Box-folder 6:15)
    - The Purpose of the Conference (Box-folder 6:16)
    - Lets Get Back to the Good Old Days in Education (Box-folder 6:17)
    - Beverly (Box-folder 6:18)
    - Early Childhood Education (Box-folder 6:19)
    - The Activities Curriculum (Box-folder 6:20)
    - Implementation of Languague Arts in Other Subject Area's (Box-folder 6:21)
    - Social Change and the Quest for Great Ideals (Box-folder 6:22)
    - Undrestanding Ways of Learning (Box-folder 6:23)
    - Commitment (Box-folder 6:24)
    - Individual Differences in and Attention (Box-folder 6:25)
    - Improving Instruction (Box-folder 6:26)
    - Some Factors Affecting Quality Teaching and Quality Learning (Box-folder 6:27)
    - Fantastic Achievement and Miseable Failures (Box-folder 6:28)
    - Quality Teaching and Quality Individuals (Box-folder 6:29)
    - Early Childhood Education (Box-folder 6:30)
    - For What Purpose Do We Dedicate This Buidling (Box-folder 6:31)
    - Learning Through Experience (Box-folder 6:32)
    - Trends in Evaluating Pupil Acheivement (Box-folder 6:33)
    - School Laws not Generally Familiar to School Pupil (Box-folder 7:1)
    - H.S. Choir (Box-folder 7:2)
    - College Marching Napper (Box-folder 7:3)
    - Big Brothers and Sisters Pep Rally (Box-folder 7:4)
    - Queens:Miss Trojan Queen (Box-folder 7:5)
    - Human Relations in the Total School Program (Box-folder 7:6)
    - Learning and the Creative Progress the Creative Act (Box-folder 7:7)
    - Moving Freedom Forward (Box-folder 7:8)
    - Understanding October 1945 (Box-folder 7:9)
    - In Spite of Odds, the Negro Contributions (Box-folder 7:10)
    - Increased Educational Responsibilities of the Principal in Today's School (Box-folder 7:11)
    - Toward Excellence in Teaching (Box-folder 7:12)
    - Health, Physical Education and Safety Recreation (Box-folder 7:13)
    - Trends in Evaluating (Box-folder 7:14)
    - Vocational Credit (Box-folder 7:15)
    - Award to Teachers (Box-folder 7:16)
    - Gentlemen (Box-folder 7:17)
    - Symphony Band (Box-folder 7:18)
    - To Dedicate This Building (Box-folder 7:19)
    - Supervising Instructions in the High Schools (Box-folder 7:20)
    - Thinking About Communism (Box-folder 7:21)
    - What are Good Human Relations (Box-folder 7:22)
    - Death is not the Enemy of Life (Box-folder 7:23)
    - The Future of Negro Teachers (Box-folder 7:24)
    - To The Graduating Class (Box-folder 7:25)
    - You Finish to Begin (Box-folder 7:26)
    - The Parents Role in Scholastics Attainment (Box-folder 7:27)
    - How Children Grow and Develop (Box-folder 7:28)
    - The Purpose of Elementary School Teachers (Box-folder 7:29)
    - Teaching and Learning (Fragment) (Box-folder 7:30)
    - Better Discipline Through Better Instruction
    - America Can and Must Be First (Box-folder 8:1)
    - Better Human Relations A Necessity (Box-folder 7:2)
    - Be Not Dismayed (Box-folder 7:3)
    - What is Teaching (Box-folder 8:4)
    - Developing a School's Philosophy (Box-folder 8:5)
    - Professional Relationship (Box-folder 8:6)
    - High School Evaluation (Box-folder 8:7)
    - Greetings to Foreign Language Teachers (Box-folder 8:8)
    - Foreign Language Conference (Box-folder 8:9)
    - Teaching Mathematics (Box-folder 8:10)
    - Evaluation (Box-folder 8:11)
    - Welcome to Mathematics Conference (Box-folder 8:12)
    - Self Studies and Self Evaluation for Professional Improvement (Box-folder 8:13)
    - Deciding Upon a Career (Box-folder 8:14)
    - The Teacher in Learning (Box-folder 8:15)
    - Fragment (Box-folder 8:16)
    - Hinedsight,Foresight, and Insight (Box-folder 8:17)
    - Trends In Eduaction (Box-folder 8:18)
    - A Tribue to Rev. George W. Watkins (Box-folder 8:19)
    - Do We Yet Have Time (Box-folder 8:20)
    - Simulation (Box-folder 8:21)
    - Better Living (Box-folder 8:22)
    - Freedom and Public Education (Box-folder 8:23)
    - The Importance of an Audio-Visual Aids to Instruction in Elementary School (Box-folder 8:24)
    - The Education of Negroes in Virginia (Box-folder 8:25)
    - An Educative Experience (Box-folder 8:27)
    - The Characteristics of a Good School Principal (Box-folder 8:28)
    - A Tribute to Dr. John H. Smythe, A Guardian of Virginia's Human Wealth (Box-folder 8:29)
    - Reading (Box-folder 8:30)
    - Why Dedicate This School? (Box-folder 8:31)
    - Including Black History in the Curriculum (Box-folder 8:32)
    - The Revolution in Education Speech (Box-folder 8:33)
    - Schools for the Sixties (Box-folder 8:34)
    - Language and Arts (Box-folder 8:35)
    - Closing Statements (Box-folder 8:36)
    - Problem Solving (Box-folder 8:37)
    - Character (Box-folder 8:38)
    - Fantastic Achievement and Miserable Fialure (Box-folder 8:39)
    - Overcoming Economic Insecurities (Box-folder 9:1)
    - The Importance of Audio-Visual Aids (Box-folder 9:2)
    - The Task of a Principal (Box-folder 9:3)
    - Teaching and Learning (Box-folder 9:4)
    - What Role Union (Box-folder 9:5)
    - Pupil Teaching Planning (Box-folder 9:6)
    - A Revolution in Education (Box-folder 9:7)
    - A Struggle for Great Ideas (Box-folder 9:8)
    - Drop Outs (Box-folder 9:9)
    - Better Human Relations a Necessity (Box-folder 9:10)
    - Improving Instruction (Box-folder 9:11)
    - The Nations Teachers (Box-folder 9:12)
    - Mathematics (Box-folder 9:13)
    - Problems Encountered in the School Program to Achieve Balance (Box-folder 9:14)
    - Freedom and Public Education (Box-folder 9:15)
    - What Shall the Schools Teach (Box-folder 9:16)
    - Passing the Torch (Box-folder 9:17)
    - Trends in Evaluating Pupil Achievement (Box-folder 9:18)
    - Opening the Doors of Oppurtunity Through Scientific Testing (Box-folder 9:19)
    - The Teachers Role in Controlling Discipline Problems (Box-folder 9:20)
    - The Revolution in Education (Box-folder 9:21)
    - A Dynamic View of Human Behavior (Box-folder 9:22)
    - In Service Study (Box-folder 9:23)
    - The Function Of School (Box-folder 9:24)
    - The Relationship of Health to Academic Achievement (Box-folder 9:25)
    - What is Meant by Mental Health in the Class Room (Box-folder 9:26)
    - This Too Shall Pass Away (Box-folder 9:27)
    - Some Problems Faced by Teachers (Box-folder 9:28)
    - Vadis (Box-folder 9:29)
    - Education and the Formation of Global Minds (Box-folder 9:30)
    - How Parents Can help to raise the Achievement Level of Teachers (Box-folder 9:31)
    - How can We Improve Standards of Achievement? (Box-folder 9:32)
    - Improving Teaching (Box-folder 9:33)
    - The Teacher (Box-folder 9:34)
    - Passing on a Heritage (Box-folder 9:36)
    - Virginia Education moves forward (Box-folder 9:36)
    - Vistiing Teachers (Box-folder 9:37)
    - The Place of Health in the Program of Public Education in Virginia (Box-folder 9:38)
    - Promoting Child Development Through Enriched Experience in Reading and Art (Box-folder 9:39)
    - Supervisor Teacher Relationships in a Program of Education (Box-folder 9:40)
    - Teaching and Learning (Box-folder 9:41)
    - Understanding Ways of Learning (Box-folder 9:42)
    - St.Paul's Place (Box-folder 9:43)
    - A Message to Parents (Box-folder 10:1)
    - How May We Improve Human Relations to World of Tomorrow (Box-folder 10:3)
    - Education in Virginia in Relations in Everyday Contacts (Box-folder 10:4)
    - Working Together to Improve Our Schools (Box-folder 10:5)
    - Teaching Questions Determine thew Quality of Thinking Pupils (Box-folder 10:6)
    - Developing A Schools Philosophy (Box-folder 10:7)
    - The Characteristics of a Good School Principal (Box-folder 10:8)
    - Greetings to Foreign Language Teachers (Box-folder 10:9)
    - An Educative Experience (Box-folder 10:10)